{
    "subject": "resource/Operation_Harpoon_(1942)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Operation Harpoon was one of two simultaneous Allied convoys sent to supply Malta in the Axis-dominated Mediterranean Sea in mid-June 1942, during the Second World War. One convoy, Operation Vigorous, left Alexandria. The other, Operation Harpoon, travelled in the opposite direction from Gibraltar. Both convoys met with fierce Axis opposition and only two of Harpoon\u2032s six merchant ships completed the journey, at the cost of several Allied warships.",
    "human_readable": "The comment of Operation Harpoon (1942) is that it was one of two simultaneous Allied convoys sent to supply Malta in the Axis-dominated Mediterranean Sea in mid-June 1942, during the Second World War.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.867404580116272,
            "question": "Were there any other Allied operations conducted simultaneously with Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7540581822395325,
            "question": "What was the significance of Operation Harpoon in World War II?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6737518906593323,
            "question": "What does it mean that Malta was 'Axis-dominated' during this time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.663236141204834,
            "question": "Where did Operation Harpoon occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.59102863073349,
            "question": "What challenges did the Allies face during Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5874391198158264,
            "question": "When did Operation Harpoon take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845621824264526,
            "question": "Who were the participants in Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47994041442871094,
            "question": "What was the primary objective of Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42892998456954956,
            "question": "What were the long-term consequences of Operation Harpoon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37142860889434814,
            "question": "How successful was Operation Harpoon in achieving its objectives?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment of Operation Harpoon (1942) is that it was one of two simultaneous Allied convoys sent to supply Malta in the Axis-dominated Mediterranean Sea in mid-June 1942, during the Second World War.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4223_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the long-term consequences of Operation Harpoon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4223_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the primary objective of Operation Harpoon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4223_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the participants in Operation Harpoon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4223_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4223_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support the statement that Operation Harpoon (1942) was one of two simultaneous Allied convoys sent to supply Malta in the Axis-dominated Mediterranean Sea in mid-June 1942, during the Second World War."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}